[{"answer": "I can't see him.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 2, "question": "UNIDENTIFIED 911 DISPATCHER: Does he look hurt to you?", "qSentId": 1}, {"answer": "Well, unfortunately, because Florida has this absurd \"Stand Your Ground\" law which makes it very, very difficult to successfully prosecute even people who may have deliberately and willfully shot because all they have to do is raise a plausible claim of self-defense and all kinds of restrictions kick in.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'd like to think it's never too late, they may get something just from the location and -- but there can't be anything left there now.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "When you saw the FBI today, pictures of them crawling all over the crime scene, is this good or is it too late for this case?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, you don't know still.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Now if that is genuine and they were inflicted by Trayvon Martin, how does that change the case you?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Let me bring in Eric Deggans here.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "How do you know that somebody didn't want to try to make it look like they've been attacked and sort of waiting for the police and there's a dead body on the ground?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, what I think is dangerous is that people take the facts that reporters are digging up and they're making suppositions.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Is it -- is it dangerous that the media keep putting this stuff out there and basically convicting or acquitting based on every new twist and turn?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's a big difference between arrest which is a formal legal proceeding for which you need probable cause under the statute.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "What do you think of this from a legal point of view?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "I'm just going to play -- just going to play a clip here, Eric, and I'll come to you after this.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Can I break in for a minute?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "Maybe both.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "UNIDENTIFIED 911 DISPATCHER: Do you need police, fire or medical?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "That's my brother.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Who was screaming there, Robert?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Well, one thing I wanted to point out.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "What did you want to say?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, I think the voice print comparison is really, really interesting.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "How significant is that?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "I don't -- I hate to judge police.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "I mean certainly it seem on the forensic side, the local police here have been incredibly lax, haven't they?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Well, that's the question that is bothering everyone.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "That it seems to have been just as skewed on the night against a young black teenage boy?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's a big difference between facts and admissible facts.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Alan, your last word?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "I'm doing great, Piers.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Senator, how are you?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "You know what, I'm not going to weigh into the -- to the particulars of this case.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "Do you believe all things considered, all the information we now have, that it would be the correct thing to do for George Zimmerman to be arrested?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, the \"Stand Your Ground\" law is to -- is to allow people to be able to protect themselves and make sure that they have the right to self-defense.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Would you accept that?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "No, it's not.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "But given the sheer number of cases now of people getting access to firearms who simply shouldn't have them, and who then go on to commit this kind of crimes, is it time for a big review of gun law in America?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Yes, you know, I'm going to make the decision not based on what's good for me or not good for me.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "At what point would you judge as a politically astute man that this would become damaging for you to stay in the race if it was perceived that you were damaging the chances of the party to defeat Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, I would say to 300 million Americans that my first act as president is to liberate you from a government program that is going to dictate to you not only your economic choices when it comes to health care, but also your religious choices when it comes to health care.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "How could you be happy, from that position, in telling 30 million Americans who are now hoping and expecting to be brought under health care cover in America when they couldn't have afforded it otherwise, you're not going to get it; that is going to be my position; my first act as president would be to throw that out, so you guys don't get health cover?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "What about people with preexisting conditions who would cease to get cover if you repealed this?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's a couple factors running around here.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Why are people buying more cars when gas prices are so expensive?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Well, I think when we had the situation in the industry, we -- we went down to support the hearings down in Washington.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Did it effectively save the industry?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Well, again, everybody has different viewpoints on this.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "So when Mitt Romney attacks the bailout, he got it completely wrong, didn't he?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Well, we actually are bringing jobs back home.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "I had Howard Schultz from Starbucks on last week, talking about a new sense of moral capitalism, where companies like Starbucks Apple and, dare I say it, Ford, rather than building big plants in Mexico, should be building plants like that in America, shouldn't you, and bringing jobs home, even if it's more expensive to do that?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Worldwide, we probably employ somewhere in the neighborhood of 160,000.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "How many people do you employ worldwide?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "In the U.S. here, we employ about 22,000 or 23,000 salaried employees, and about 45,000 to 50,000 hourly employees.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "How many of that would be in America?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "No, that's hourly and salaried.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "And what was that initial figure you gave me, the 160,000, are they all salaried or are they hourly and salaried?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120402pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "As a business?", "qSentId": 529}]